Mum, look!
妈妈   看
Lingling has got some interesting photos.
玲玲有一些有趣的照片
Can I see them, Lingling?
我能看看吗   玲玲
Of course.
当然可以
They are photos of me and my family in China.
它们是我和我中国的家人的照片
This is Xinjiang.
这是新疆
It's in the west of China. I went there last year.
它在中国西部   我去年去了那边
Did you go with your parents?
你是跟你父母一起去的吗
Yes, I did.
是的
We stayed with my grandma for a week in July.
七月我们和奶奶呆了一个星期
The mountains are really beautiful.
这些山真的很美
This is Hainan. It's in the south of China.
这是海南   它在中国南部
Who is this?
这是谁
It's my uncle.
这是我叔叔
He lives there with his three children.
他和他的三个孩子住在那儿
My cousins visit Beijing every year.
我的表兄弟每年都会来北京
Oh yes, I remember!
哦   是的   我记得
I met them in June! They're Li people.
我六月的时候见过他们   他们是黎族人